Guide to the Howard Gillette Papers, 1826-2018 MS0644.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Class Divide: Yale '64 and the Conflicted Legacy of the Sixties, 1955-2017; Series 6
  - Lea, Sydney: Six Sundays Toward a Seventh, 2012; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Lieberman, Jethro K.: Liberalism Undressed, 2012; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Liberman, Joseph I: The Power Broker, 1966; Series 6 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Musil, Robert K.: Hope for a Heated Planet, 2009; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Powers, Thomas: The Military Error, 2008; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Powers, Thomas: Vietnam, The War at Home, 1973; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ranney, Edward: The Lines, 2014; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Roderick, Tom: A School of Our Own, 2001; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Rogers, James: A Bull in China, 2007; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Rogers, James: Investment Biker, 1994; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Roth, William: Movement, 1986; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Schaefer and Voors: Vision in Action, 1986; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Smith, John Thomas II: Cars, Nuclear Diplomacy, and the Law, 2012; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Speth, James Gustave: Angels by the River, 2014; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Thompson, Tony: Eat your Heart Out, Ho Chi Minh, 2011; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Van Dyke, Jon M.: Who Owns the Crown Lands of Hawai'i?, 2008; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Wilbur, John S. Jr.: Split/Vision, 2014; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Yale 1964: Class Book, 35th Reunion, 1999; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Yale Class Book, Volume CXXIII, 1964; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Yale 1964: Class Directory, 40th Reunion, Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Yale 1964: Later Life, 25th Reunion Classbook, 1989; Series 6 (Box 26)
  - Yale 1964: Ten Years Out, 1974; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 18)